mckinney.com 2019-07-02

# Privacy - McKinney

McKinney Ventures, LLC ("McKinney") respects the privacy of its website users and has created this privacy policy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy. The following discloses our information gathering, use and dissemination practices solely for the website located at www.mckinney.com (the "Website").

By using or accessing the Website, you signify your assent to our Privacy Policy. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY YOU MAY NOT ACCESS OR OTHERWISE USE THE WEBSITE.

**Personal and Non-Personally Identifiable Information**

When using the Website, you may choose to provide McKinney with certain personally identifiable information about yourself ("Personally Identifiable Information"). Personally Identifiable Information can include your name and email address. In addition, we may also collect non-personally identifiable information, such as IP host address, pages viewed, browser type and other data, and may aggregate any information collected in a manner which does not identify any individual ("Aggregate Information").

**Information Usage**

Unless disclosed otherwise at the time of collection, we do not share any Personally Identifiable Information you submit through the Website with any unaffiliated third party, unless it is necessary to respond to your inquiry, or to comply with applicable law. We may use Aggregate Information to improve and enhance your experience on the Website and for our research activities. For example, we may share Aggregate Information with unaffiliated third parties, such as business partners, in an aggregate, anonymous form, which means that the shared information will not contain nor be linked to any Personally Identifiable Information.

We will not sell your Personally Identifiable Information to any third party not affiliated with McKinney without your consent, except we may do so without your consent in connection with the sale or merger of McKinney or the division responsible for such services.

Please note that we reserve the right to access and/or disclose Personally Identifiable Information and non-personal information we gather as required by courts or administrative agencies and to the extent required to permit us to investigate suspected fraud, harassment or other violations of any law, rule or regulation, the Website rules or policies, or the rights of third parties or to investigate any suspected conduct which we deem improper.

**Security**

The security of your Personally Identifiable Information is very important to us. We have put in place reasonable physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard the information we collect. We cannot state that we can completely guarantee that communications between you and McKinney or information stored on the Website or our servers will be completely free from unauthorized access by third parties such as hackers. Therefore, by using the Website, you acknowledge that the potential for unauthorized access still exists and you agree to assume this risk.

**Protection for Children**

We have no intention of collecting personal information from children under the age of 13. When we become aware that personal information from a child under 13 has been collected without such child's parent or guardian's consent, we will use all reasonable efforts to delete such information from our database.

**Changes to Policy; Opt-Out Process**

We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions from this policy at any time. However, if at any time in the future we plan to use Personally Identifiable Information in a way that differs from this policy, we will post such changes here and provide you the opportunity to opt-out of such differing uses. Your continued use of the Website following the posting of any changes to this policy means you accept such changes. We give you the option to remove your Personally Identifiable Information from any lists that we maintain of users. All unsubscribe or opt-out requests should be sent to us at [hello@mckinney.com](mailto:hello@mckinney.com) and we will process your request within a reasonable time after receipt. We are not responsible for removing your Personally Identifiable Information from the lists of any third party who has previously been provided your information in accordance with this policy.

**Website Terms and Conditions**

Use of this Website is governed by, and subject to, the Website Terms and Conditions. Your use, or access, of the Website constitutes your agreement to be bound by these provisions.

**Contact**

Contact: For questions or concerns relating to privacy, we can be contacted at: [hello@mckinney.com](mailto:hello@mckinney.com)

**United States of America:**

Our Website is maintained in the United States of America. By using the Website, you expressly authorize us to export your Personally Identifiable Information to the USA and to store and use it in the USA as specified in this policy.

**Effective Date**

This privacy policy is effective and was last updated on July 20, 2015.
